Preliminary Guide to the Robin Chandler Lynn Duke Papers, circa 1930-2003
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession (1999-0157)
  - Packard Foundation -- Board of Directors (Box 3)
  - UN-USA Board of Directors (Box 3)
  - U.S.-Japan Foundation (Box 3)
  - Misc. Conferences (Box 3)
- Accession (1999-0289)
  Copy clippings and make use copies of videos before patron use.
  - Subject Files (Box 1)
    Primarily materials relating to major organizations and interest in population control
    - National Abortion Rights Action League (NARAL) (Box 1)
      Member update; two folders of misc. information, data, publicity materials; correspondence; and videocassette, Choice for America Initiative.
    - National Campaign to Prevent Teen Pregnancy (Box 1)
      Publicity campaign materials (postcards, Spanish and English language pamphlets) sponsored by Teen People Magazine; Correspondence, invitation to 1999 anniversary events; research and reports; fact sheets.
    - Packard Foundation (Box 1)
      Faxed clipping regarding Foundation's commitment to environmentalism and reproductive rights; binder of materials from Population Committee Meeting, 1999; correspondence; folder marked "Packard May 1999," binder of materials on executive session of Board of Trustees, 1999; annual report, 1997; materials relating to a trip to Mexico; materials relating to a trip to Kyoto, Japan; folder of materials for Committee on the Board, list of programs denied funding; agenda and resolutions for Board of Trustees meeting; Population Committee Meeting, 1993.
    - Planned Parenthood (Box 1)
      1997-1998 annual report; summary of proceedings of Roe v. Wade at 25 symposium; press release about Vatican stance on Kosovar refugees; 1996 annual report.
    - Population Action International (Box 1)
      Briefing cards on sexual and reproductive health (2 copies); agenda of 1999 meeting of board of directors; Fact Sheet #9; newsletter of US NGOs sponsored by PAI, fact list reprinted by PAI (5 copies); binder of materials from annual meeting of board of directors, 1999; folder of correspondence and reports as received as a member of board of trustees (labeled "Guggenheim"); "Profiles in Carbon: an update on population, consumption, and carbon dioxide emissions."
    - Population Crisis Committee (Box 1)
      International Human Suffering Index; 1990 Report of Activities; informational brochure; 25-year history; fact sheets; by-laws; correspondence; pamphlet on China's family planning program; annual reports from 1992, 1994, and 1995.
    - Center for Gender Equality (Box 2)
      Information from the Advisory Board, Study of the Impact of Religious Organizations on Gender Equality, Surveys of Women.
    - Council of American Ambassadors (Box 2)
      Meeting of the Board of Directors, 1999.
    - Friends of Art and Preservation in Embassies (Box 2)
      Remarks by the President and First Lady, Memorandum on Meeting with Ambassador Pickering, Tenth Anniversary Annual Events.
    - Institute of International Education (Box 2)
      Board of Directors Annual Meeting, 1999, Memorandum, Annual Events 1999.
    - Harvard School of Public Health (Box 2)
      Materials relating to committee on population and international health; biennial report 1996-1998.
    - International Flavors and Fragrances, Inc. (Box 2)
      Folder containing materials for annual conference of shareholders; folder containing materials for annual meeting of Board of Directors.
    - National Mother's Day Committee (Box 2)
      Newsletter, photo and flyer (RDC received honors as one of 7 "outstanding mothers" of 1999); press kit.
    - National Park Foundation (Box 2)
      Correspondence, photographs.
    - U.S.-Japan Foundation (Box 2)
      Binder of materials from annual meeting of the Board of Trustees, 1998; binder of materials from meeting of the finance committee, 1999; binder of materials from annual meeting of the Board of Trustees, 1999; correspondence.
    - United Nations Population Fund (Box 2)
      Battery-powered device for determining population growth; correspondence; draft of "Programme of Action of the Int'l Conference on Population and Development"; three-part video series on "Population: Choice or chance?"
    - Women's Capital Corp. (Box 2)
      Curriculum vita, January 1999.
  - Correspondence (personal and professional) (4 folders) (Box 3)
    Miscellaneous correspondence is found throughout the collection, especially professional correspondence, although these four folders are specifically marked as such. Five additional folders also primarily contain correspondence but are marked with these headings:
    - Rockwell (3 folders) (Box 3)
    - Joan Gunter/Southampton L.I.U. (1 folder) (Box 3)
    - Jefferson Awards (1 folder) (Box 3)
  - Subject/Miscellaneous Files
    - Protocol (Box 3)
      Memos from the State Department, Invitation to Dinner with President Johnson, Photographs, Newspaper Clippings, Programs for State Visits, Remarks of the Ambassador of Spain.
    - Smithsonian (in Protocol A Folder) (Box 3)
      Correspondence.
    - Blair House (in Protocol A Folder) (Box 3)
      Several Histories of Blair House, Correspondence, Programs, Radio Transcript.
    - Money (Box 3)
      Jewelry Catalog, Various Board Contribution Forms, Political Solicitations, National Center for Children in Poverty.
    - Israel/ Council of American Ambassadors (Box 3)
      Packard Foundation Materials, Information on Health and Family Planning in Mexico, Materials from the National Population Council, Summary of Council of American Ambassadors Trip to Israel.
    - Sharon Camp (Box 3)
      Memos and faxes.
    - Steven W. Sinding (Box 3)
      Curriculum Vitae (several copies).
    - Luncheon for Secretaries of UN Ambassadors (Box 3)
      1982 Luncheon Invitation, Draft of Speech, Letters of Thanks.
    - Global Committee of Parliamentarians on Population and Development (Box 3)
      Statement on Population Stabilization by World Leaders, Notes of Thanks, Correspondence, Photographs, Materials from All-Africa Conference on Population and Development.
    - Centre for Development and Population Activities (Box 3)
      Correspondence and News Clips.
    - Appointment book pages (Box 3)
    - Materials from years in Spain (Box 3)
    - Telephone Conversation Summary of A.B. Duke with Pres. Johnson (Box 3)
    - Clippings on Blair (Box 3)
    - House Redecoration (Box 3)
    - Funeral of A.B. Duke (Box 3)
    - Faxes (Box 3)
    - Philippines (Box 3)
    - Additional miscellaneous items (Box 3)
    - Taxes (Box 3)
      Draft from Alfred Koss (faxed), Itineraries, Meetings, Correspondence.
    - New York Times Article (Box 3)
      Responses to a profile of Robin Chandler Lynn Duke in the New York Times.
    - Philippines (Box 3)
      Pamphlet entitled Partnership or Disengagement, Correspondence, Agenda for the Council on Foreign Relations, Philippine Economic Information, Materials on World Population Control.
  - Correspondence and Miscellaneous Files (Box 4)
    Four (4) Unlabeled Folders Containing Correspondence, News Clippings, Photographs, and other Miscellaneous Items.
  - Subject Files
    - PAI Board Meeting, 1996 (Box 4)
      Pamphlet from the Board of Directors, United Nations Materials on Africa
    - Planned Parenthood Federation of America (Box 4)
      World Bank Materials on Improving Reproductive Health, Correspondence
    - Speeches, July 1998 (Box 4)
      Atlantic Monthly Article on the Future of Population, New York Times Article on Politics, Reproductive Freedom News, World Population Data Sheet, Recent Abortion Legislation and Court Decisions, Packard Foundation Population Program 1998.
    - Tokyo International Symposium (Box 4)
      RCD Notes on the Symposium, Talking Points, Photographs.
    - Seoul, Korea (Box 4)
      Notes from RCD's Trip to Seoul, Itinerary for the Trip.
    - Angier Biddle Duke Funeral (Box 4)
      News Clippings, Itinerary.
    - American Express Tax (Box 4)
      Financial Papers, Invitation.
    - Airle Foundation (Box 4)
      Financial Papers, Itinerary for Trips to Japan, Information on Foreign Service.
    - Editorials (Box 4)
      Editorials on Abortion, Writings by RCD, Oral Presentation.
    - W.A.C. (World Affairs Council) (Box 4)
      Materials from Seeking the Fountain of Youth in a Changing Environment, List of Political Contributors, Draft of Letter.
    - IIE (Box 4)
      List of Board of Trustees, Week in Preview, Apr. 12, 1999-Apr. 16, 1999.
    - Cairo Notes (Box 4)
      Newspapers and News Clips, Information on Women in Cairo, Paper entitled Population Policy for the 21st Century, Faxes, Materials from International Conference on Population and Development 1994 (held in Cairo).
  - Oversize Materials (Box 5)
    Newspaper and Magazine Clippings, Magazines -- Home and Garden July 1994 and Town and Country January 1998, New York Times Magazine Oct. 1997, Morocco United States Oil Colloquium, Miscellaneous Items.
  - Packard Foundation Board of Trustees Meeting, 1999 (Box 6)
  - Photograph Album -- Japan (Box 7)
  - Photograph Album - Japan (Box 8)
  - Photograph Album - Japan (Box 9)
- Accession (2000-0013)
  - Professional Files, 1992-1999 (29 folders) (Box 1)
    Primarily materials relating to Duke's activism and participation in major organizations for population control. Other files pertain to her years with her husband, A.B. Duke, when he served as Chief of Protocol under President Kennedy. Organizations represented include the Japan Foundation, Friends of Art and Preservation in Embassies, Planned Parenthood, Population Action International, Packard Foundation, National Abortion Rights Action League, and the United Nations Association of the U.S.A. There are clippings, correspondence, faxes, printed materials, and other related items.
  - Professional Files, continued (12 folders) (Box 2)
    These files are similar including clippings, some speeches, programs, and correspondence. There are a number of videotapes on a variety of subjects, primarily population control, but one is a film about Duke. There are also forms of ID and proofs from her 25th wedding anniversary party.
  - Binders And Printed Materials, 1998-1999 (Box 3)
    Binders contain material for boards of directors meetings and include materials related to Population Action International. Other printed material relates to the National Campaign to Prevent Teen Pregnancy. Duke's address book is also included.
  - Professional And Personal Files, 1974-1999 (Box 4-5)
    These files include correspondence, personal and professional clippings for 1977-1978, materials related to her campaign for the unexpired term of Mayor-Elect Koch in New York's 18th Congressional District, some speeches, and more materials related to her duties as a population control activist.
  - Scrapbook (Box 6)
    Contains primarily photographs, clippings.
  - Plaque for Duke from the French ambassador - Manhattan's Woman of Charity (Box 7)
  - Printed materials (Box 7)
  - Commemorative Stamp Pin Collection (Box 7)
  - Photograph of Duke (Box 8)
  - Scrapbook primarily devoted to President Kennedy's Assassination and the work of A.B. Duke's protocol office in the days following. (Box 8)
- Accession (2000-0176)
  - Contents of box 1: (Box 1)
    - Clippings (Box 1)
    - Correspondence, (5 folders) (Box 1)
    - Itineraries (Box 1)
    - Photographs, (2 folders) (Box 1)
    - Printed Material
      - Miscellaneous, (5 folders) (Box 1)
      - Pro-Choice (Box 1)
    - Speeches/Writings (Box 1)
  - Contents of boxes 1-2: (Box 1-2)
    - Subject Files
      - Angier Biddle Duke Lecture (Box 1-2)
      - National Campaign to Prevent Teen Pregnancy (Box 1-2)
      - International Flavors and Fragrances (Box 1-2)
      - Friends of Art and Preservation in Embassies (Box 1-2)
      - Population Action International (Box 1-2)
      - National Abortion Rights Action League (NARAL) (Box 1-2)
      - United States Committee for the United Nations Population Fund (Box 1-2)
      - Lasker Awards, 2000 (Box 1-2)
      - United Nations Association (Box 1-2)
      - United States-Japan Foundation, (2 folders) (Box 1-2)
      - United States-Japan Foundation: Scrapbook (Box 1-2)
      - Geoffrey Beene (Box 1-2)
      - Institute of International Education (Box 1-2)
      - David and Lucille Packard Foundation (Box 1-2)
  - Contents of box 3: (Box 3)
    - Scrapbooks, (4 volumes) (Box 3)
  - Contents of box 4: (Box 4)
    - Scrapbooks, (4 volumes) (Box 4)
  - Contents of box 5: (Box 5)
    - Scrapbook (Box 5)
  - Contents of box 6: (Box 6)
    - Scrapbook (Box 6)
    - Proofs from box 1. (Box 6)
  - Contents of box 7: (Box 7)
    - Scrapbook (Box 7)
- Accession (2000-0341)
  - Printed material regarding reproductive rights and democracy rights, including from the Institute for Democracy Studies, 1999-2000 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, invitations, information packets, and printed material from conferences and meetings, 1991-2000 (Box 1)
    Organizations represented include the American Institute for Public Service, The Albert Lasker Medical Research Awards, and the Center for Reproductive Law and Policy. Duke won an Albert Lasker Public Service Award in 1991.
  - 2 black-and-white photographs, one of Robin Chandler Duke, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Magazines (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, notes, information packets, and printed material from Duke's involvement in various organizations, including meetings she attended, 1998-2000 (Box 2)
    Organizations include Population Action International, The Future of Children, Harvard School of Public Health, Friends of Art and Preservation in Embassies, and the Presbyterian Church, USA.
  - Correspondence, notes, information packets, and printed material from meetings Duke attended for various organizations, 1998-2000 (Box 3)
    Organizations include Institute for Democracy Studies, RB Asset, Inc., Planned Parenthood Federation of America, Inc., Friends of Art and Preservation in Embassies, and International Flavors and Fragrances, Inc.
  - 2 VHS videocassette tapes regarding family planning (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, notes, information packets, and printed material from meetings Duke attended for various organizations, 1999-2000 (Box 4)
    Organizations include U.S.-Japan Foundation, Planned Parenthood Federation of America, Inc., Friends of Art and Preservation in Embassies, International Flavors and Fragrances, Inc., United States Committee for the Population Fund, and The David and Lucille Packard Foundation.
  - Correspondence, notes, information packets, and printed material from meetings Duke attended for various organizations, 1999-2000 (Box 5)
    Organizations include Planned Parenthood Federation of America, The David and Lucille Packard Foundation, World Childhood Foundation, Inc., and the U.S.-Japan Foundation.
  - One audio CD-RW from World Childhood Foundation, Inc. (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, notes, information packets, and printed material from meetings Duke attended for various organizations, 1998-2000 (Box 6)
    Organizations include the United Nations Association of the United States of America and the World Childhood Foundation, Inc.
  - One black-and-white photograph of Duke with other attendees at the Angier Duke Memorial Lecture Series, New York, 1999 (Box 6)
- Accession (2001-0147)
  - Contents of box 1: (Box 1)
    - UNIPA (Box 1)
    - Council of American Ambassadors, 2001 (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous including fliers, correspondence, and information folders (Box 1)
    - Personal letters, 1960s, (2 folders) (Box 1)
    - Photograph of Robin Duke (Box 1)
  - Contents of box 2: (Box 2)
    - Mexico City Conference, 1984 August (Box 2)
    - The Honorable Silvio Conte (Box 2)
    - International Population Conference in Mexico City, 1984 August, (5 folders) (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1990s (Box 2)
  - Contents of box 3: (Box 3)
    - PAI (Box 3)
    - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 3)
    - UNESCO, (2 folders) (Box 3)
    - China Trip, 1978
      - Letters and Memos (Box 3)
      - RCD Notes (Box 3)
    - United States Senate, Committee on Foreign Relations (Box 3)
    - UNESCO
      - Duke Luncheon honoring Mr. Amadou-Mahtar M'Bow, 1984 April 12 (Box 3)
      - Letters and Memoranda (Box 3)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 3)
    - Hong Kong/Vietnamese Closed Camps (Box 3)
    - U.N., New York City Commission (Box 3)
    - Sasakawa
      - Guest Lists, 1975 October (Box 3)
      - Visit, 1975 (Box 3)
      - Letters, 1975 February-December (Box 3)
  - Contents of box 4: (Box 4)
    - Humanae Vitae, Encyclical (Box 4)
    - Governor Hunt, Duke Fundraising Dinner at River Club, 1984 February 29 (Box 4)
    - Draper Fund, Responses to Trip Reports (Box 4)
    - Carbons of Letters Sent Out
      - A (Box 4)
      - B (Box 4)
    - China Trip, Reports on China, 1978 (Box 4)
    - Chronological Letter Carbons
      - 1977, (2 folders) (Box 4)
      - 1978 (Box 4)
    - NARAL - State Affiliates (Box 4)
    - Chinese Contraceptives (Box 4)
    - Protocol (Box 4)
    - Democratic Congressional Campaign Committee, Women's Congress Council Reception, 1984 July 10 (Box 4)
    - Democratic Senatorial Campaign Committee (Box 4)
    - Campaign, Reception and Dinners (Box 4)
  - Contents of box 5: (Box 5)
    - THIRTEEN, Events (Box 5)
    - CPC
      - Michaele Vollbracht's Central Park Carousel Benefit, 1982 November 1 (Box 5)
      - Letters (Box 5)
      - Board of Trustees (Box 5)
      - Financial Information (Box 5)
      - Frederick Law Olmsted Award Benefit Luncheon, 1983 May 3 (Box 5)
    - Friends of Art and Preservation in Embassies (Box 5)
    - Dreyfus Life, Board Members and Meetings (Box 5)
    - Blair House, (2 folders) (Box 5)
    - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 5)
    - Correspondence, 1980s
      - A-B (Box 5)
      - C-D (Box 5)
      - E-F (Box 5)
      - G-H (Box 5)
  - Contents of box 6: (Box 6)
    - Correspondence cont., 1980s
      - I-J (Box 6)
      - K-L (Box 6)
      - M-N (Box 6)
      - O-P (Box 6)
      - Q-R (Box 6)
      - S-T (Box 6)
      - U-V-W (Box 6)
    - Population Crisis Committee (Box 6)
    - Overseas Press Club (Box 6)
    - Morocco and Spain (Box 6)
    - Southampton College, 1981 July 24 (Box 6)
    - Hans Morgenthau, 1981-1982 (Box 6)
    - Appeal, 1981 June 2 (Box 6)
    - Spanish Institute, 1981 November 11 (Box 6)
    - Sakura Matsuri, 1982 May 1 (Box 6)
    - USJF Board Meeting, 1982 May 28 (Box 6)
    - J. Hopkins University, 1982 September 28 (Box 6)
    - Holyland, 1982 November 17 (Box 6)
    - Sakura, 1983 April 30 (Box 6)
    - Pundits, 1984 February (Box 6)
    - Amb. Okawara, 1984 April (Box 6)
    - Population, California, 1984 September (Box 6)
    - Hill and Knowlton, 1984 October (Box 6)
    - Daniel Ortega, FPA, 1984 October (Box 6)
    - FIT, Central America, 1985 March 15 (Box 6)
    - Reidsville, North Carolina, 1985 May 23 (Box 6)
    - Southampton, N.Y., LIU Reception, 1985 June 1 (Box 6)
    - Correspondence, 1984, (2 folders) (Box 6)
    - Conference, Chicago, 1984 April (Box 6)
    - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 6)
    - H & K Correspondence, 1986 (Box 6)
    - Security Bank (Box 6)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 6)
  - Contents of box 7: (Box 7)
    - Central America, 1984 May (Box 7)
    - Statements and Reports, (3 folders) (Box 7)
    - Statements and Reports, General (Box 7)
    - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 7)
    - PRODEMCA, Correspondence, 1986 (Box 7)
    - PAI (Box 7)
    - Duke, Historic Letters, (3 folders) (Box 7)
  - Contents of box 8: (Box 8)
    - Friends of Art and Preservation Embassies, Board of Directors Winter Meeting, New York, 2000 (Box 8)
    - U.S.-Japan Foundation, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 2001 April 22-23, (2 folders) (Box 8)
    - Albert and Mary Lasker Foundation (Box 8)
    - Planned Parenthood, Vermont (Box 8)
    - Planned Parenthood (Box 8)
    - First Lindbergh Awards Dinner, 1978 (Box 8)
  - Contents of box 9: (Box 9)
    - Correspondent's Notebook, The Inauguration (Box 9)
    - GALA - Honoring Women (Box 9)
    - Scrapbook of the Dukes while in Copenhagen, 1968-1969, (includes photographs) (Box 9)
    - Photo Album of Duke at the Planned Parenthood of Thailand, 1976, (includes photographs) (Box 9)
    - Photo Album of CBFPS in Thailand, 1976, (includes photographs) (Box 9)
    - Draper World Population Fund Report, 1977 (Box 9)
    - Women Directors of the Top 1000 Corporations, 1993 (Box 9)
  - Contents of box 10: (Box 10)
    - Birth Control in America: The Career of Margaret Sanger by David M. Kennedy, 1970 (Box 10)
    - Miscellaneous Norwegian Embassy Information including various booklets and folders (Box 10)
  - Contents of box 11: (Box 11)
    - Miscellaneous Norwegian Embassy Information including various booklets and folders (Box 11)
    - Newspaper clippings and Correspondence, 1960s (Box 11)
    - Photo Album of Duke in an Asian Country (Box 11)
  - Contents of box 12: (Box 12)
    - Blair House (Box 12)
    - Correspondence, 1960s, 1980s, 2001 (Box 12)
    - NIA-PCC Executive Meeting, 1988 (Box 12)
    - Newspaper, The Exonian, 2001 April (Box 12)
    - Jefferson Award Nominations, 1993 (Box 12)
    - PAI (Box 12)
    - Negatives (Box 12)
  - Contents of box 13: (Box 13)
    - Minnesota Meetings Speech (PCC/PIPR), St. Paul, MN, 1984 November 5 (Box 13)
    - NARAL, Congressional Information, (2 folders) (Box 13)
    - National Abortion Federation (Box 13)
    - Municipal Art Society of New York, The RCD, Member (Box 13)
    - NARAL, Arts, Letters, and Politics Inc., Letter received for Dec. Benefit (Box 13)
    - Record of Messages (Box 13)
    - UNESCO, (2 folders) (Box 13)
    - For the Record, 1981 October 19 (Box 13)
    - El Salvador, 1981 November-December (Box 13)
    - Morocco, 1982 November-December (Box 13)
    - Tokyo, 1982 March (Box 13)
    - For the Record, 1982 May 24 (Box 13)
    - Tokyo, 1982 November (Box 13)
    - Tokyo, 1983 May (Box 13)
    - ABD for the record, 1983 July 28 (Box 13)
    - Costa Rica, 1983 September (Box 13)
    - Memorandum For the Record, 1984 March (Box 13)
    - Morocco, 1984 (Box 13)
    - For the Record, HAK, CFR, 1984 April (Box 13)
    - Tokyo, 1984 May 19 (Box 13)
    - Bogota, 1984 August (Box 13)
    - For the Record, Morocco (Box 13)
    - El Salvador, 1985 March (Box 13)
    - North Carolina, 1985 May 3 (Box 13)
  - Contents of box 14: (Box 14)
    - Biographies of Ambassador Duke (Box 14)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 14)
    - General, (3 folders) (Box 14)
    - Statements, Press Articles (Box 14)
    - General Correspondence (Box 14)
    - Board of Trustee Correspondence (Box 14)
    - Orfila Luncheon, 1983 October 12 (Box 14)
    - April 12 Luncheon (Box 14)
    - 21 Club Foundation Meeting, 1983 February 24 (Box 14)
    - The Bill (Box 14)
    - Hidalgo Statements (Box 14)
    - General (Box 14)
    - Directors (Box 14)
    - WAC Membership (Box 14)
    - Press Releases/Articles (Box 14)
    - Progress Reports/Brochure (Box 14)
    - Ellis Island Preservation Project (Box 14)
  - Contents of box 15: (Box 15)
    - National Council of World Affairs Organizations (Box 15)
    - Executive Forum (Box 15)
    - By-laws (Box 15)
    - Advisory Council (Box 15)
    - World Affairs Council, 1986 (Box 15)
    - Correspondence
      - 1985 (Box 15)
      - 1984 (Box 15)
      - 1983 (Box 15)
      - 1982, (2 folders) (Box 15)
      - 1981 (Box 15)
      - 1984 (Box 15)
      - 1985 (Box 15)
    - Statue of Liberty Correspondence, 1986 (Box 15)
    - General (Box 15)
  - Contents of box 16: (Box 16)
    - Plen - United States of America (Box 16)
    - Newsclippings, 1960s and 1970s (Box 16)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Programs, 1930s-1980s (Box 16)
    - Scrapbook of Duke's Social Activities, (includes photographs) (Box 16)
    - UNESCO (Box 16)
  - Contents of oversize box 17: (Box 17)